

DEBERA MILLER

debbiemiller1995@gmail.com | 216-536-8637

Summary

Self-starter, attention to details and trained in operation and AML compliance reviews. Looking for an Internal Auditor position. I have over ten years of Internal Auditing experience to offer.

Skills

- Time management
- Multitasking
- Training and development

- Attention to detail
- Microsoft Office
- Excel

Experience

Internal Auditor/ Monitor

09/1999 - 08/2018

Checksmart | Cleveland, Ohioi

Monitor:

- Performing audits of assigned functions including operational and AML compliance audits.
- Audited information and implemented all data into spreadsheets using Excel.
- Performed testing of internal controls based upon strict regulations, including compliance in accordance with the methodology.

Internal Field Auditor 2007 - 2017

- Traveled through out the US.
- Performed audits of operational and financial areas to assure regulations, procedures and AML compliance were being adhered to.
- Communicated audit findings by preparing final reports.

Manager 1999 - 2007

- Manage and grow the business.
- Oversaw performance and quality of service for eight employees.
- Drove improvements to the growth, collections and compliance of the business.
- Efficiently addressed customer issues to ensure quick and successful resolution.
- Oversaw all daily operations of one store locations.

Teller Trainer 07/1990 - 11/1998

Dollar Bank | Cleveland, Ohio

- Conducted classes for all new tellers on, cash handling, compliance, procedures and products.
- Hands on training of the POS.
- Administering and grading of all tests.

Teller and New Accounts 1990 - 1996

- Processed customer's transactions promptly and accurately and gave excellent customer service.
- Balanced all daily operations of the branch.
- Opened new customer accounts including checking, savings and processed new loans.

Education and Training

West Tech | | Cleveland, Ohio, Cuyahoga